A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Bursar, Reports, Series 6 FA812
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Bursar, Reports, Series 6
1919-1930, 1932-1934
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
Rockefeller University
FA812
1.76 Cubic Feet 4 boxes
4 boxes
Biographical/Historical note
Missing Title
1911-1917 Herman Goepper called Assistant Treasurer until 1914
1917 Harry Dewitt Burrell
1917-1946 Albert Dovall Robertson
1946-1966 Charles Petrzelka
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 214-6
Conditions Governing Access note
Records are open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Other Finding Aids note
FA213 Rockefeller University records, Bursar, Administrative Correspondence, Series 2.
Arrangement
Chronological.
Scope and Contents
Disbursements and receipts.
World War I; Federal government -- United States; United States; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research. War Demonstration Hospital; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research; Rockefeller University
- Reports: Bursar's receipts and disbursements, 1919-1930, 1932-1934; 6; 1.76 Cubic Feet
  Scope and Contents note
  Consists of monthly reports from the bursar surveying receipts and disbursements at the Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research. The first report for each fiscal year covers the period July 1 to September 30. No separate reports, were made for July and August. The reports for 1919 include expenditures and balances for the Rockefeller Foundation-funded War Demonstration Hospital at RIMR.
  Folder titles indicate the first report in each folder.
  Subjects include the War Demonstration Hospital.
  Arrangement note
  Arranged in chronological order.
  - Rockefeller Foundation War Activities
    - 1919 January 1-1919 December 31 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 1919 July 1-1919 December 31 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1919 July 1-1920 March 31 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1919 July 1-1920 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1920 July 1-1921 January 31 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1920 July 1-1921 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - 1921 July 1-1921 December 31 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - 1921 July 1-1922 March 31 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - 1921 July 1-1922 June 30 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1922 July 1-1922 December 31 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 1922 July 1-1923 March 31 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - 1922 July 1-1923 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 1923 July 1-1923 December 31 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1923 July 1-1924 March 31 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - 1923 July 1-1924 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - 1924 July 1-1924 December 31 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - 1924 July 1-1925 March 31 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1924 July 1-1925 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - 1925 July 1-1925 December 31 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - 1925 July 1-1926 March 31 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - 1925 July 1-1926 June 30 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - 1926 July 1-1926 December 31 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 1926 July 1-1927 March 31 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1926 July 1-1927 June 30 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 1927 July 1-1927 December 31 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 1927 July 1-1928 March 31 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1927 July 1-1928 June 30 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1928 July 1-1928 November 30 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 1928 July 1-1929 February 28 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1928 July 1-1929 June 30 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 1929 July 1-1929 December 31 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1929 July 1-1930 March 31 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - 1929 July 1-1930 June 30 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - 1932 July 1-1932 December 31 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - 1932 July 1-1933 March 31 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 1932 July 1-1933 June 30 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 1933 July 1-1933 December 31 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 1933 July 1-1934 March 31 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 1933 July 1-1934 June 30 (Box 4, Folder 5)